Nurullah Altas

+90 (543) 680-5930 DOB: 03/11/1993 nurullahaltas93@gmail.com

I have four years of experience in front-end development. Working in multinational companies, I took my ability to be a team player and communication skills to higher levels. I have a strong academic background. I am the 1281st person in Turkey to take the university entrance exam out of approximately 1.9 million people. I completed the 4-year program in 3 years at Boğaziçi University, one of the most prestigious universities in Turkey.



Experiences

September 2019 - Present

SmartGift

Smartgift is a platform building brand loyalty, show employee appreciation and corporate gifting. The project developed on **React** with **Context API**, **hooks** and functional components.

February 2019 - September 2019

Adesso - IT & Business Consultancy

Adesso is a German company which targeted solutions for core business processed based on latest IT trends. On here, I completed three projects named Optica Omnia, DekaBank and Apollo Optik.

Apollo Optik: Worked on an German online store project at Apollo selling optical products such as eyeglasses, lenses, etc. On this project we used **React**, **react-redux** for state management and **redux-saga** for creating complex side effects without getting bogged down by the details. I developed the product detail page, and I was responsible for performance optimization and SEO.

DekaBank: This project is basically development of a web application for German bank which automates the process and determine the market comformity for different assets of the bank. On this project I also used latest **React** library, **rxJs** for asynchronous communication.

Optica Omnia: The new Optica software for German medical supply stores, supports and documents the entire supply process. This project required highly strong frontend development skills such as latest **Angular** framework, **ngRx** for state management, **rxJs** for observable handling and 80% test coverage using **karma** for quality assurance November 2018 – February 2019

Exagate

Exagate provides high-tech solutions by taking into consideration to have maximum service time in IT infrastructures. I was responsible the module that enables the 2D sketches displayed to be in 3D form with virtual reality. For doing this, I used d3.js for drag and drop for generating 2D sketches, AFrame for converting sketches into VR on an Angular project.

April 2017 - November 2018

5v5 Information Technologies

5v5 Information Technologies is a software consultant company produces solutions for technology companies. I worked with Biletix(TicketMaster) which one of our partners. The project was related to event organizators' report tool. I completed this project Angular 2 using TypeScript.

Technologies

- React
- React-redux
- Redux-saga
- Angular
- ngRx
- rxJs
- Webpack
- Git
- TypeScript
- Sass SCSS
- Material Design
- Bootstrap
- Karma

Education

Managament Information Systems, Boğaziçi University. 2015 – 2018

Language

Turkish: Native English: Fluent